Privacy Policy
--------------

Re-TV collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers, servers, and apps typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Re-TV's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Re-TV's visitors use its websites and apps. From time to time, Re-TV may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its websites and apps.

Re-TV also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Re-TV only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Re-TV's websites and users of Re-TV's apps may choose to interact with Re-TV in ways that require Re-TV to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Re-TV gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Re-TV - for example by purchasing a product - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Re-TV collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Re-TV. Re-TV does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related or app-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

Re-TV may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites and the usage of apps created by Re-TV. For instance, Re-TV may monitor the titles of videos selected within an Re-TV app. Re-TV may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Re-TV does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Re-TV discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Re-TV's behalf or to provide services available on Re-TV's websites and apps, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Re-TV's websites and apps, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Re-TV will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Re-TV discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Re-TV believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Re-TV, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Re-TV website or app and have supplied your email address, Re-TV may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Re-TV and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Re-TV takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Third-Party Advertising Companies

Re-TV may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites or use our apps. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites and apps in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here [https://thenai.org/opt-out/](https://thenai.org/opt-out/).

Business Transfers

If Re-TV, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Re-TV goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Re-TV may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Copyright & DMCA

Re-TV respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects its users to do the same. In accordance with the Digital Millenium Copyright Act of 1998, the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at [http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf](http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf), Re-TV will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement committed using Roku channels built using Re-TV's services. Please click this link for more information about how Re-TV handles claims of copyright infringement: [http://www.InstantTvChannel.com/copyright](http://www.instanttvchannel.com/copyright).

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Re-TV may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Re-TV's sole discretion. Re-TV encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Re-TV Networks

##### © Re-TV Networks | All Rights Reserved
